# 我们一起面对命运 #
We face the music together
# 堵上我们的一切 #
And throw our hats in the ring
# 面对各种天气 #
Facing all kinds of weather
# 无所畏惧 #
And not afraid of anything
# 当太阳升起时 我们会在路上 #
When the sun comes up, we'll be on our way
# 我们不在乎目的地 #
And we don't care where we land
# 不管浪有多高 #
And the waves are high,
# 但我们不回头 #
but we won't turn round
# 因为我们手牵手 #
'Cause your hand is in my hand
# 并且 哦-哦 #
And, oh-oh
# 你让我感到无人能敌 #
You make me feel invincible
# 因为是你与我一起 #
'Cause it's you and me
# 穿过风浪 #
Through the wind and hail
# 向世界起航 #
Setting sail into the world.
好的 天啊 今天真的很棒
Okay. Oh, gosh. This was great.
你想亲我一下告别吗 就现在
Do you want to kiss me good-bye, here, now?
好啊
Um, yes.
我 我以为我要把你送回门口呢
I-I was gonna walk you to your door.
- 哦 - 你不是就住在前面街角吗
- Oh. - 'Cause you live on the corner, right?
是啊 但是没事的 你不用的
Yeah, but that's okay. You don't even have to.
在这里就行
You could just do it here.
为什么 你爸爸在外面
Why? What... what, is your dad waiting outside
- 拿着猎枪等着你吗 - 差不多吧
- with a shotgun or something? - Oh, kind of.
什么
What?
不是的
No.
不是 是...
No. It's, uh...
- 是 古泽敏 - 啊
- It's Guzmin. - Ah.
嗯 他从阿尔巴尼亚来的
Yeah, he's from Albania.
- 你懂的 他在劳动营长大的 - 嗯
- You know, he grew up in a labor camp. - Right.
- 他的父母曾经是政治激进分子 - 哦
- His parents were political activists. - Oh.
- 他们在他小时候就被逮捕了 - 真惨
- They were arrested when he was a kid. - Shit.
好吧 我... 我感觉你没当回事
You know, I... I feel like you're not taking this seriously.
古泽敏到底是谁
Who the hell is Guzmin?
那就是古泽敏
That is Guzmin.
你的门卫吗
Your doorman?
不 他不仅仅是门卫
No, he's more than a doorman.
这 这很难解释
It's-it's very hard to explain.
他成为了我的...
He's become a...
该死
Oh, shit.
天啊 不要
Oh, my God, no.
- 别这样 不 - 为什么不行
- Don't do that, no. - Why not?
- 拜托 - 不
- Come on. - No.
我... 最好不要
I... I wouldn't do that.
他怎么想对你很重要吗
Is it important to you what he thinks?
不 天啊 当然不了
No. Oh, my God, no.
不 我是个独立的女人
No, I'm an independent woman,
我不需要任何人帮我做决定
and I don't need anyone to help me make up my mind.
好吧
Okay.
好了 我得走了
All right, I better go.
- 什么 - 嗯
- What? - Yeah.
你的出租来了
Here's your taxi.
- 走吧 - 什么...
- Let's go. - What? Wha...
我今晚很高兴
I had a really great time tonight.
你愿意再来一次吗
Um, do you want to do this again?
当然了 我...
Yes, I...
- 嗯 - 我是说 我今天和你聊的很愉快
- Yeah. - I mean, I loved talking to you this evening.
我明晚有空
I'm free tomorrow night.
我给你打电话 - 好
I'll call you. - Okay.
晚安 古泽敏
Good night, Guzmin.
那是谁
Who was this?
那是马克
That was Mark.
我不喜欢他
I did not like him.
省省吧
Save it.
他不是你的类型
He is not for you.
他很弱还没有自制力
He is a weak man with no self control.
你在三十尺外怎么知道的
How can you tell that from 30 feet away?
你通过狙击枪的瞄准镜能了解一个人的很多事
You learn a lot about a man through the scope of a sniper rifle.
- 他不会给你打电话的 - 会的
- He will not be calling you. - Oh, yeah.
他绝对会的
He absolutely will be calling me.
永远 他永远不会给你打电话的
Ever. He will never be calling you.
天啊 我今晚看起来多美啊
God, I looked so good tonight, okay?
我很幽默 我很有才情
I was so funny. I was scintillating.
我喷了我的无花果香水
I wore my fig perfume,
据说让人难以拒绝
which is apparently impossible to resist.
那你... 你想打赌吗
I mean, do you... do you want to bet?
我不会打百分百会赢的赌的
I cannot bet on a certainty.
这不符合我的原则
It is against my principles.
晚安 米歇尔小姐
Good night, Miss Mitchell.
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
感到很性奋 我感到很性奋
Feeling frisky. I'm feeling frisky.
好的
Okay.
他不会给你打电话的
He will not be calling you.
他永远不会给你打电话的
He will never be calling you.
去你的
Fuck you.
有马克的消息吗
Any news from Mark?
没 没有 我没看 我不知道...
No. No, I haven't even checked. I don't...
这不是我人生的全部
It's not my whole life.
- 祝你愉快 米歇尔小姐 - 你也是
- Have a good day, Miss Mitchell. - Yep. You, too.
该死的 古泽敏 算你厉害
Damn it, Guzmin. You're good.
所以 你的工作是评论书籍
So, you review books for a living,
然后你和一个门卫住在一栋楼里吗
and you live in a building with a doorman?
是啊 那个公寓很多年了一直是我们家的
Yes. The apartment has been in my family for years,
所以房租也一直是八十年代的水准
so the rent is stuck in the '80s.
加上我读书很快
Plus I'm a really fast reader.
所以你一周读多少书
So how many books can you read in a week?
有时一天一本
Oh, sometimes I read one a day.
- 什么 - 是啊
- What? - Yeah.
所以这让你 十分聪明吗
So does that make you, like, really bright?
不 我只是知道很多事实而已
No. I just know a lot of facts.
我就像有脚的百科全书
I'm like a Wikipedia page with legs.
好吧 我一年一本就不错了
Yeah, well, I'm lucky if I read one a year.
抱歉
Sorry.
嗯 但是... 你很帅
Yeah, but... you're good-looking.
总不能两者兼顾吧
I can't have both, right?
既聪明又帅
Smart and so good-looking.
- 好吧 - 又不是童话
- Yeah, okay. - It's not a fairy tale.
谢谢你送我回家
Thank you for seeing me home.
不客气
You're very welcome.
我喜欢这样
Oh, I like that.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- Yeah? - Yeah.
所以 这是去你家或者去我家的时刻吗
So, is this a "Your place or mine" Moment?
怎么了
What's up?
这样吧 来我家
You know what? Mine.
真的吗
Yeah?
真的 去他的
Yeah. What the hell?
- 晚上好 古泽敏 - 米歇尔小姐 晚上好
- Good evening, Guzmin. - Miss Mitchell. Good evening.
晚安
Good night.
泰德
Ted.
Ted?
泰德
该死
Damn it!
古泽敏 早上好
Gugmin. Morning.
- 你好吗 - 早上好
- How's it going? - Morning.
和平常一样
Another day, another dollar?
你回来了
You're back.
带着面包和牛角面包
With bread and croissants?
你这个漂亮的英国混蛋
You beautiful British bastard.
早安 亲爱的
Morning, darling.
刚刚去给我们买早餐了
Just popped out to get us some breakfast.
嗯 好的 当然
Oh, yeah, sure. Of course.
快上来
Yeah, come on up.
早安 我的宝贝
"Good morning, my darling. Morning... "
- 你进来了么 宝贝 - 我讨厌他
- Didn't you get in, my darling? -  I don't like him.
- 什么 - 泰德
- What? - Teddy.
- 你就见了他半分钟 - 那已经够久的了
- You met him for 30 seconds. - Even that was too long.
嗯 好的 他非常的友好
Okay, well, he's perfectly nice.
好吧 这可能是一种习惯
All right, it's probably a cultural thing.
你对别人太苛刻了
You're way too hard on people.
古泽敏 你不能对每个人我带回家的人
Guzmin, you have to stop failing everyone
- 都有意见 - 他没什么脑子
- that I bring home, okay? - He is empty-headed.
你是有博士学位的智慧女人
You are a very bright woman with a PhD.
我只是怕你吃亏
I'm only thinking of your interests.
给他一个机会 好吗
Please give him a chance, all right?
他非常有礼貌 他 他还很性感
He is very polite, and he is, he is sexy
他还完成了
- and he is accomplished
并且他回来了
and he is in the apartment.
- 吃牛角包吗 - 我什么时候错过
- Croissants? - Have I been ever wrong?
好的 太奇怪了 他就在这
Okay, this is getting weird. He's right here.
- 你在和谁说话呢 - 没什么 拜
- Who are you speaking to? - No one. Bye.
- 嗨 泰德  早啊 - 嗨
- Hi, Ted. Good morning. - Hi.
- 刚才是古敏吗 - 是古泽敏
- Was that, uh, Gugmin? - Guzmin.
- 对 那个保安 - 是 门卫
- Yeah, that security guard. - The doorman.
对 他看起来很好
Right. He seems like such a nice chap.
我们刚才在楼下交谈很愉快
We had a right laugh downstairs.
对 他就是太过热情了
You know, he's just super friendly.
哦真的么 你还笑了
Oh, yeah? You had a right laugh?
- 是啊 - 好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
# 就要碎了 #
# about to crack #
- 早上好 米歇尔 小姐 - 你好 古泽敏 你过得怎么样
- Good evening, Miss Mitchell. - Hi, Guzmin. How are you?
挺好的
No complaints.
今天看了什么呢
What did you read today?
- 给我讲讲有趣的事 - 嗯 好啊
- Tell me an interesting fact. - Oh, yeah.
嗯 你知道昙花一现
Okay. Um, do you know where the term
这个词从哪来的吗
"Flash in the pan" Comes from?
淘金者
Gold prospectors.
在筛子里看到闪光的金子
Seeing a flash of fool's gold in the sieve
或是一支不会射出子弹的步枪
or a musket flash that doesn't shoot a bullet.
- 对么 - 对
- Am I right? - Yeah.
非常准确 你是对的
That's-that's exactly it. Yeah, you're right.
我以前都不知道
I didn't know that.
你看起来不太一样 你换发型了吗
You look different. Did you change your hair?
没啊 哪不一样了呢
No. How different?
感觉你有一点变化
Something has changed about you.
嗯 那可能是我有点伤心
Oh, well, uh, yeah, maybe I'm a bit sad.
为什么有点伤心呢
Why a bit sad?
泰德 先生今晚没来么
Isn't Mr. Ted gracing us tonight?
没 事实上 我们分手了
No. Actually, we broke up.
我很遗憾
I am so sorry.
他曾昙花一现
He was a flash in the pan.
对没错
Right. Yeah.
你的眼光很犀利 古泽敏
Your instincts are very spot-on, Guzmin.
有点不可思议
It's sort of uncanny.
我们这行 就要学会看人
Where I'm from, you learn to read a man.
好吧 如果你能把它包装起来
Well, if you could bottle that up
卖给美国的年轻女性
and sell it to young American women,
你就不再是门卫了
you wouldn't have to be a doorman anymore.
我当门卫很开心
I'm very happy with being a doorman.
我不是 我很抱歉 我不是这个意思
I did not... I'm sorr... I didn't mean it like...
- 我很抱歉 - 没事的
- I'm so sorry. - Okay.
- 晚上好 - 晚上好
- Good evening. - Good evening.
九月二十三 下午两点  一稿截至期 露丝  九月二十六 下午两点  修改稿截至期 露丝
米歇尔小姐
Miss Mitchell?
- 有什么需要帮忙的 - 不用了 谢谢
- Can I get you anything? - No. Thanks.
就有点头疼
I just, um, got a headache,
阿司匹林吃完了 我就过一条街
and ran out of aspirin, so I'm just running across the street.
我有艾德维尔（一种药品布洛芬品牌）
I have Advil, somewhere.
是偏头痛 对
It's a migraine. Yes.
我也需要一些治胃不舒服的药
So I need something for an upset stomach, too.
盖胃平颗粒 需要吗
Gaviscon?
我马上回来
Be back in a sec.
# 她们 比你还有钱 #
# Eeny, meeny, miny, mo money than you, bitch #
# 我一点都不在乎 #
# My M.O. Is I just don't give a shit... #
# 现在我戴着珠宝 #
# Now I'm drippin' in jewels #
六十五块五 要袋子吗
65.50. Do you want a bag?
# 以前住警局 现在我戴着珠宝 #
# Was livin' in the P's, now I'm drippin' in jewels #
# 哇哦  #
# whoo! #
晚安
Good night.
好吧好吧好吧
Okay, okay. Okay, okay, okay.
没事的
It'll pass.
我不能和一个我不爱或者不信任的
I can't bring a baby into the world with a man
男人生孩子
that I don't love or trust.
你知道 孩子需要父母
You know, a baby needs two parents.
一个宝宝需要一个母亲和一个父亲
A baby needs a mom and a dad.
这话是不是太保守了
What conservative nonsense this is?
我 不是这个意思 显然
No, I don't mean it like that, obviously, I...
我是说 像我 我的成长方式就是有
I just mean, like, the way that I was brought up, you know?
父母两个人
With two parents.
哦 我的天啊 我的爸妈
Oh, my God, my parents.
我的天 他们会怎么说我
Oh, my God, what are they gonna say about this?
一个小姑娘去了城里
Their little girl comes to the city and then,
就一年 就怀孕了
within a year, is pregnant,
甚至都没有能在一起的人
and not even with a man she intends on staying with.
你知道 他们对他很兴奋
You know, they were so excited about him.
他们以前觉得他像休・格兰特
They thought he was like Hugh Grant, and now he's like...
现在他确实像他
... Hugh Grant.
谁关心你父母怎么说呢 或者他们做事的方式
Who cares what your parents say? Or the way they did things?
四个街区外有个诊所
There's a clinic four blocks away.
你知道 我可以的 这些会过去的
You know, I could... this can go away.
当然
Sure.
没人会批评你 做你想做的
No one is going to judge you. Do what you wish.
别因为畏惧而不做
But don't do it because you're scared.
在生活中你一定要有自己行动
You must own your actions in life.
我自己做不了
I can't do this on my own.
找一个地方养大孩子
A village brings up a child.
纽约是个非常好的地方
And New York is a very great village.
现在你先好好休息
Now get some good sleep.
明天又是崭新的一天
Tomorrow is a brand-new day that's never been touched.
你曾大费周章保护我不受这些坏男人伤害
You have made such a big thing out of protecting me
现在似乎又是在
from all these bad men, and now it's like
鼓励我独自生活
you're encouraging me to live life alone.
但你不再孤单了
But you're no longer alone.
# 在这个明亮的城市 #
In this city of light
# 我看见... #
I see...
- 抱歉我迟到了 - 不 没关系
- Sorry I'm late. - No, that's... that's fine.
- 你好 - 嗨
- Hello. - Hi.
谢谢你来见我
Um, thank you for, um, meeting me.
我从英格兰来的 这里是大都市中心
Oh, I'm from England. It's the center of urbanity.
我们仍能偶遇彼此
We can totally still meet up.
- 你看起来不错 - 谢谢
- You look great. - Oh, thank you.
你想喝什么
What are you having?
有个孩子...
Uh... A baby.
那是种新推出的新潮鸡尾酒吗 天啊
Is that one of those new hipster mocktails? God.
我想我还是要冰红茶吧
I think I'll just stick with an iced tea.
你可能得喝点更烈的东西
Yeah, you should probably have something a little stronger.
请问两位喝什么
Hey, can I get you something to drink?
- 喝酒 - 等等
- Have alcohol. - Just a minute.
好的
Okay.
所以当时...
So when, um...
那个...
the... uh...
我...
I...
你还好吗
You okay?
深呼吸
Just take a deep breath.
关于这事
You can have as much or as little as you want
你要多要少都无所谓
to do with this.
你不必负责
Um, there is no obligation.
我会尊重你的任何决定
Either way, I... I will respect your decision,
但是 我决定了
but, uh, I have decided
我想要这个宝宝
that I want to have this baby.
但是我... 我
But I... I...
会很想有你在身边
would love for you to be around.
还有... 但是
And, um... but, yeah.
你还是还以像以前那样过日子
Your life can just keep going on being the same as it was before.
好的 太好了
Okay, great.
好的
Okay.
你想和我一起为宝宝起个名字吗
Do you want to come up with some names together?
你自己看着办吧
Uh... or you do that.
怎样都行
Either way.
米歇尔小姐
Miss Mitchell.
你这是在干什么啊
What the hell do you think you're doing?
天啊 古泽敏 我想我这是第一次
Oh, my God, Guzmin, that's the first time
听到你真的生气了呢
I've heard you really angry, I think.
你这种状况还在这个忙碌的城市骑自行车
Cycling around this crazy city in your condition.
拜托 我戴着头盔呢
Oh, come on, I'm wearing a helmet.
你肚子里的宝宝也戴着头盔吗
Is your son wearing a helmet?
那个只有一条小鱼那么大的宝宝...
That little child, only the size of a small fish...
也戴着头盔吗
is he wearing a helmet?
说到小鱼
Speaking of small fish...
看看这个
... check that out.
你是第一个看到这些图像的人
You're the first person to see these.
你怀了四胞胎吗
You're having quadruplets?
什么 不是 这是同一个宝宝
What? No, that's the same baby.
- 我开玩笑的 - 当然
- It's a joke. - Oh, yeah.
这是脊柱
So that is the spine.
这是脑袋
And then that's the head.
这里面好像有整个宇宙
It's like the whole universe in there.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
我很好
Fine.
我只是从没见过这种图片
I've just never seen this type of pictures before.
给你
Here.
我有四张呢
I have four of them.
好的 回见
All right, I'll see you.
就这样
Yes.
# 那个坠落凡间的女孩 #
The girl who fell to Earth
- 别 - 好的
- No! - Okay.
# 所以拆了它 粗暴对待... #
So tear it down, play it rough...
好的
Okay.
# 你不想搞砸这件事 #
You don't mean to mess it up...
我爸吗 不会的 他为什么来
My dad? No. Why?
- 不 我是说你宝宝的爸爸
- No, I mean the baby's daddy.
对 我都忘了还有个宝宝了
Right. I forgot there's a baby.
不 当时我的羊水提前破了
Um, no. My water broke early,
我发了短信给他 但他出城了
and, uh, I texted him, but he's out of town.
- 理解
- Understood.
其实我们不是夫妇
We're not a couple, you know.
他是个很好的人 他是个好人 但是
Oh, he's a great guy, he's a good guy, but, um,
我们不是 其实...
we're not, you know, um...
我不知道我为什么要和你说这些
I don't know why I'm telling you this.
我也不知道 但我听到你说的了
I have no idea, but I hear you.
老实说 我们更喜欢这样
And, to be honest, uh, we kind of prefer it this way,
- 因为我们碰到过很多晕过去的爸爸
- because we have a lot of fainters.
婴儿的心跳很好
Baby's heart is good.
来得有点早 但现在不要阻止他或她
A little early to the party, but no stopping him or her now.
我还没想好要不要上镇痛泵
I haven't decided yet if I'm gonna get an epidural,
我过会再决定也可以吧
but I can decide later, right?
比如 如果真的很疼
Like, if it gets really bad.
如果吗
"If"?
用力
Keep going!
用力 马吉
Keep going, Maggie.
加油
Come on now.
加油 你得用力
Come on, you got to keep pushing.
好的 好的
Good, good.
很好
Oh, oh, oh, very good!
你想摸摸你小孩的头吗
Ah. You want to feel your baby's head?
- 我不知道 我要吗 - 是的是的 来吧
- I don't know. Do I? - Yeah, yeah, come on.
这是你的孩子
That's your baby.
天啊 老天
Oh, my God! Jesus Christ!
好的 没事 我们再来一遍
Okay, all right. Let's get ready to go again.
- 我做不到 不行 - 加油
- I can't do it. No. - Come on.
不不不 我太累了 我做不到
No, no, no, I'm too tired. I can't do it.
- 我做不到 我没力气了 不行 - 再使劲用力一次
- I can't do it. I'm too exhausted. No. - One more big push.
就万事大吉了 好吗
And got to give it everything you got, okay?
不行 我做不到 我做不到
No, I can't do it. I can't do it.
因为你宝宝的心跳刚刚有点急速
'Cause your baby's heart rate, it's a little fast right now,
我们需要你配合
and we need you to work with us,
我们得把你宝宝拉出来
and we need to get your baby out.
再用力一次 就这样 就这样
One more. Here we go. Here we go.
加油 加油
Come on. Come on.
就这样 加油
That's it, come on.
用尽全力 来 用力
Everything you got. Here we go.
再使劲用力
One more big push.
很好
Good.
干得漂亮 马吉
Well done, Maggie.
啊 我的天啊
Oh! Oh, my God.
真好看
Beautiful.
- 做得很棒 - 谢谢
- Good job. - Thank you.
# 只有小丑才会玩那些气球 #
Only clowns would play with those balloons
# 我的歌声如此落寞 #
Passive when I'm in record...
以后的吧
I will.
# 日日夜夜 #
Day and night
# 我守望着你 #
I'm watching you...
她又不是炸弹
She's not nitroglycerin.
我不想弄醒她
I don't want to wake her.
啊 别出声 纽约
Oh, shush, New York.
闭嘴
Shut up.
# 妈妈的胸脯难忘掉 #
Titties that live on and on
我来开
I'll get it.
# 难忘掉 #
On and on
只有小丑才回去玩那些气球
Only clowns would play with those balloons
让自己一副芭比模样
to look like Barbie for
真棒 真棒
Ooh. Bravo, bravo, bravo.
- 你喝牛奶吗 - 不
- Do you drink milk? - No.
- 不吗 - 妈妈们不喜欢孩子喝牛奶
- No? - Moms don't like baby milk.
- 她们不喜欢吗 - 我的天
- They don't? - Oh, my God.
非常抱歉 但愿我来得不是太晚
I'm so sorry. I hope I'm not too late.
- 非常感谢你照看她 古泽敏 - 完啦
- Thank you so much for watching her, Guzmin. - Oh, no!
不好意思 突然不知从哪里冒出来一个会
Oh, I'm so sorry. That meeting came up from out of nowhere.
- 嗨 嗨 宝贝熊熊 - 没关系的
- Hi! Hi, baby bear. - It was not a problem.
照顾她我很开心
She was a pleasure to watch.
- 你在干嘛呀 - 我在我家里
- What are you doing? - I'm at my house.
你在家里吗
You're at your house?
我不在的时候你们俩玩什么啦
What did you guys do while I was gone?
我们去了一个大房子 里面有各种各样的动物
We went to a big room where there was all the animals
肚子里塞着东西 我还吃了古泽敏的午餐
full of stuffing, and then Guzmin's lunch.
美国自然历史博物馆
The American Museum of Natural History.
我没去过 里面挺有意思的
I had not been. It was fun.
- 我们现在要上楼了 好吗 - 我要拿着这个
- We have to go upstairs now, okay? - SARAH: I can hold this.
- 多谢你了 - 有求必应
- Thank you so much. - Always.
好啦 来 我们走
Okay, all right. Let's go.
我们上楼啦 我们上楼啦
We're going. We're going.
我们... 谢谢
We're... thank you.
- 说拜拜 - 拜拜
- Okay, say, "Bye!" - Bye!
拜拜 晚安
Bye! Good night!
- 拜拜 莎拉 - 拜拜
- Bye-bye, Sarah. - Good-bye!
不可以背着我自己去看恐龙哦
Don't go see the dinosaurs again without me.
我不会的 我保证
I will not. I promise.
哦 不要
Oh, no.
又来了
Not again.
很好笑 真的
Very funny. Yeah.
不
No.
我怎么也睡不着
I just can't sleep.
你要吃点安眠药吗
You want an Ambien?
不用 谢谢
No, thank you.
我就是太兴奋了 我签了一份工作
I'm just excited. I got a job offer.
一份杂志的文学评论编辑
The editor of a literary supplement of a magazine.
太好了 米歇尔小姐
Fantastic, Miss Mitchell.
人们是时候领略你的才华了
It's about time people started to see your talents.
可地点在洛杉矶
But it's in L.A.
好吧
Okay.
我不知道我是否该让她在洛杉矶长大
I don't know if I want to bring her up in L.A.
- 她是个纽约人- 她不会有事的
- She's a New Yorker. - She will be fine.
她没法步行上学 而且那里...
She won't be able to walk to school, and it's...
烟雾弥漫 人情虚假
it's smoggy there and it's... it's phony.
你什么时候走
When are you leaving?
我们还在做计划 考虑这样做的可能性
Uh, we're just making plans now, seeing if it's possible.
没什么事是不可能的
Everything is possible.
她会想念这座城市
She'll miss the city.
以及这栋大楼
And this building.
还有你
And you.
我没有意见 马吉
No complaints, Maggie.
失陪
Excuse me.
放松
Relaxed.
别刻意搞笑
But don't try to be funny.
你并不是很搞笑
You're not very funny.
- 什么... - 他很搞笑
- What is... - He is funny.
- 好吧... - 那要怎样做
- Well... - What is this about?
就... 冷静些
Just... be cool.
不过不是洛杉矶的那种冷酷 不要高冷
But not L.A. Cool, not frosty cool.
展现你的可爱
Just be your lovely self.
你好 你好 你好 你好
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
嗨
Hi.
看看你
Look at you.
- 我不敢相信 - 见到你真是太好了
- I can't believe it. - It's so good to see you.
我想你见一个人
I want you to meet someone.
嘿 朋友
Hey, man.
这位是丹尼尔 这位是古泽敏
This is Daniel. This is Guzmin.
我的老朋友
My old friend.
见到您很开心
Pleased to meet you, uh...
听说我得通过一项测试
I hear I have to pass some sort of test?
- 你通过了 - 很好
- You passed it. - Cool.
- 可我做了什么 - 没什么
- What did I do? - Nothing.
我在她眼里得知的 就在看到她的那一刻
I saw it in her eyes, the moment I saw her.
古泽敏
Guzmin.
我看的从来不是男人 马吉
I was never looking at the man, Maggie.
我看的是你的眼神
I was looking at your eyes.
- 不算难嘛 - 别搞砸了
- Well, that was easy. - Don't blow it.
嗨 调皮鬼 过来这里
Hello, little monkey. Come here.
看看你
Look at you.
看看你 看看你 我的调皮鬼
Look at you, look at you, my little monkey.
看看你
Look at you.
我真不敢相信她都八岁了 更不敢相信她现在在这里
I can't believe she's eight. I can't believe she's here.
旅途如何 顺利吧
So how was your airplane flight? Good?
顺利 一路上...
Yeah, it was, uh...
你今天最想做什么
What do you most want to do today?
# 一个跌落尘世的姑娘 #
The girl who fell to Earth
# 你的心我来抚慰 你的梦我来守护 #
I'll comfort you, I'll warm your dreams